

INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL AND
BANK OFFICER

Details

trellebogade1,11-tv-2630 højtaastrup

2630

Denmark

91430426

PLACE OF BIRTH

Khalkhal

Links

linkd in

Skills

Financial Analysis(Forex, stock market)

Computer Skills

Microsoft Office Word

Microsoft Office Excel

software skills: on time. fast learner. adapted stressful work and hardworking

Languages

English(IELTS6)

danish(MODUL3)

Persian

Turkish/azarbayjani

Hobbies

playing chess journey cycling

Profile

15 years of experience in banking industry:

Executed customer transactions, including deposits, withdrawals, money orders, ATM and checks.

Experience of working in the banking facilities for two years including receiving form applications, document collection and documents verification process (credit score, credit history, income details, employment status and KYC details)

Experience of working for credits department for 2 years including collection process such as sending dunning letters to customers or calling customers.

11 years of experience in Forex and stock market operation, professional in technical analysis using pattern, Elliot waves, familiarity with fundamental concepts in financial markets such as GDP, NFP, CPR etc.

Employment History

Bank officer at Iranian Bank (Maskan), Zanjan and Ardabil

APRIL 2007 - MAY 2022

www.bank-maskan.ir

Bank is one the important bank in IRAN.

2007-2017: cashier position in Maskan bank:

I had been working as a cashier in Maskan bank for 10 years. During that period, I was responsible for performing various duties such as opening and closing accounts, deposits, withdrawals, money orders and checks. In addition, I used to open internet bank accounts and mobile bank. I had to educate

Costumers how to work with internet bank site and mobile bank applications as well.

2017-2020: working in banking facilities section

At 2017, I changed my position and I started working in banking facilities section. In this section, apart from dealing with bank customers, I was responsible for some other tasks such as reviewing and analyzing loan procedures, performing semi-annual account credit, limit reviews and credit increase review requests from financial service. I also need to carefully analyze documents and inform client of missing items.

2020-2022: working in collection debt process section

In this 2-year period, I took the responsibility for collecting bank debts which were overdue.

finally i am ontime, hardwork and fast learner person, who knows word, excell, html5,css3 and java script

Education

Master's Degree/Industrial engineering_ system & productivity management, Islamic Azad University Qazvin Branch, Qazvin

OCTOBER 2012 - JANUARY 2017

bachelor Degree/ Applied Mathematics, Tabriz University, Tabriz

OCTOBER 1999 - FEBRUARY 2004